{
    "id": "e80326eae35443a09ee5025605f3dd85",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to go now. Here now is an ............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "preposition",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0e14cdee83dd4276977d74b918470dfe"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you doing there? Here there is a/an ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "conjunction",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "63e3cbe41ba04ec294d3263101e52772"
        },
        {
            "question": "He left ten minutes ago. Here ten is a/an ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "41a2781a8f7b4b96a961390ee8316269"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a mistake in line  Here in is a/an ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c74d7d2df2bc419a9ae2f9f302319c58"
        },
        {
            "question": "Masons build houses. Here build is a/an ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "preposition",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1616fa4f672c49cf95632363023fcf39"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though she was unwell, she went to work. Here though is a/an ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "preposition",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17152a822c31436fa179ac0aef6590f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been reading since morning. Here morning is a/an .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "noun",
                "pronoun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2442dd8d5b8c44539a5ae7df11532d0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He died two years ago. Here ago is a/an .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eda0a95ec7c6428497d762b691c29f0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "As she was late, we went without her. Here as is a/an ..............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "preposition",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bd1c17b91898479aa6778a060d1605fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Nile is the longest river in the world. Here Nile is a/an .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "collective noun",
                "proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f4068b78412c468bb5ad4e5b96c0c952"
        },
        {
            "question": "What happened to you? Here you is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c0c68bc3a40498eb1cd9d75aca5af09"
        },
        {
            "question": "My family live in different parts of India. Here different is a/an .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "adjective",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbc2cf66ac0947ae96ed4fce8a3e1047"
        }
    ]
}